Hello friends, now we will know
about the dividend of this company, okay, so stay
with me friends, you can see its name, you can
also see the price, so let's see the
dividend of this company, okay,
how much dividend does this company give and whether it has
given dividend this year or not, you
can see, if it has not given dividend this year yet, you
can see its ex-dividend and
can see the percentage of dividend, you
can also see the account rupees, okay, you can see that in 24 years, it has
given division only twice, this
company gives division twice a year, it gives division
in the month of June and October,
okay,
and you
can see that in 24 years, it had given 60 and 55
dividends, so that's all for today, God
bless you.